好吧 你看 这是新招
Okay, see, this is new.
- 她是蹲在... - 是啊
- Is she lowering herself... - Yeah.
他脸上吗
onto his face?
她似乎 要坐在他脸上
She seems to be taking a seat on his face.
真是... 太奇怪了
Which is... well, it's so weird,
我见过人类 坐在各种地方
'cause I've seen humans sit on things.
通常都是
Normally, it's stuff like,
- 地铁什么的 - 地铁 对
- like the subway or something. - Like the subway, yeah.
- 还有... - 或者椅子
- I mean, like... - Or like, chairs.
- 长椅 座位 - 长椅 没错
- Benches. Seats. - Benches, yeah.
- 对 座位 统称座位 - 就是座位
- Yeah, seats. Seats in general. - Just seats.
我从没见过 坐在别人脸上
I've never seen someone seat on a face.
这看起来... 我也说不好
I mean, it looks... I don't know.
有点...
Eh, that's kinda...
- 怎么了 - 没事 没事
- What? - No, nothing. It's fine.
对了 你要带什么 去参加派对
Uh, what are you bringing to the party, by the way?
我... 找到了块饼干
Oh, um, I'm just... I found a cracker over there.